Do you ever feel like a plastic bag,
drifting through the wind, wanting to start again?
Do you ever feel, feel so paper thin,
like a house of cards, one blow from caving in?
Do you ever feel, already buried deep,
six feet under screens and no one seems to hear a thing?
Do you know that there's, still a chance for you,
cause there's a spark in you?
You just gotta ignite the light,
and let it shine, just own the night,
like the 5th of July.
Cause baby you're a firework,
come on show em what you're worth.
Make em go ah, ah, ah, as you shoot across the sky.
Cause baby you're a firework,
come on let your colors burst.
Make em go ah, ah, ah,
you're gonna leave em all in awe.
You don't have to feel, like a wasted space,
your original, cannot be replaced.
If you only knew, what the future holds,
after a hurricane, comes a rainbow.
Maybe a reason why, all the doors are closed,
so you could open one that leads you to the perfect road.
Like a lightning bolt, your heart will glow,
and when it's time you'll know.
You just gotta ignite the light, and let it shine,
just own the night, like the 5th of July.
Cause baby you're a firework,
come on show em what you're worth.
Make em go ah, ah, ah,
as you shoot across the sky.
Baby you're a firework,
come on let your colors burst.
Make em go ah, ah, ah,
you're gonna leave em all in awe.
Boom, boom, boom,
even brighter than the moon, moon, moon.
It's always been inside of you, you, you,
and now it's time to let it through.
Cause baby you're a firework,
come on show em what you're worth.
Make em go ah, ah, ah,
as you shoot across the sky.
Baby you're a firework,
come on let your colors burst.
Make em go ah, ah, ah,
you're gonna leave em all in awe.
Boom, boom, boom,
even brighter than the moon, moon, moon.